gibbon.co 2015-03-13

# Privacy Policy - Gibbon

Last updated: 28 January 2014.

Gibbon B.V. ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of service and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting [gibbon.co](https://gibbon.co/) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

For the purpose of the Dutch Data Protection Act (the Act), the data controller is Gibbon B.V. having its principal place of business in Leiden, The Netherlands.

#### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

**Information you give us.** You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site [gibbon.co](https://gibbon.co/) ( **our site** ) or by corresponding with us by e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our services, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site, enter a competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, e-mail address, personal description and photograph and password.

**Information we collect about you.** With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:

technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;

information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); knowledge you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**Information we receive from other sources.** We may receive information about you if you use Facebook, LinkedIn or Twitter to join our site. In this case you will be asked to approve that we collect certain information from these third parties and may combine this information with data we collected on this site. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

#### Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

#### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

**Information you give to us.** We will use this information:

to provide you with the services that you request from us and to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;

to provide you with information about other services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;

to notify you about changes to our services;

to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

**Information we collect about you.** We will use this information:

to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about knowledge that may interest you or them;

to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;

to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

to allow you to participate in interactive features of our services, when you choose to do so;

as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;

**Information we receive from other sources.** We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

#### Disclosure of your information

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with you.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If Gibbon B.V. or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Gibbon B.V., our customers, or others.

#### Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Gibbon B.V. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where you have chosen a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

#### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right at any time by contacting us at [privacy@gibbon.co.](mailto:privacy@gibbon.co)

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

#### Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.

#### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

#### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [privacy@gibbon.co.](mailto:privacy@gibbon.co)
